[The D Dorm]
Honestly, I miss you every day.
I long for you.
Dreaming of you every single night.
My shining moon.
My everlasting love.
I cannot stand it.
I miss you, Gaysorn.
Grandpa,
what's wrong with you, huh?
Well, I am disappointed!
I thought Dew's grandmother
was Gaysorn,
the one I missed dearly,
but she is not.
My heart
is shattered.
Sadhu. I hope Grandpa's soul
shatters, just as he said.
Sadhu!
How dare you curse me like that?!
Huh?!
Grandpa, he's the first person we asked.
Why are you so down?
"The first person"?
What does that mean?
It was "the first time," Auntie Duang.
It's my first time
eating at your restaurant.
I usually just order food
to eat in my room.
Come more often, then.
Your grandpa used to come here a lot.
Before he died,
he said he'd lower my rent.
Lower your rent?
When did I say that, huh?!
Anus Duang!
Oh, is that so?
But is "Anus Duang" your full name?
Look.
[Duangjai's Kitchen, Made-to-Order Food]
"Duangjai."
Wait,
Gramps only calls me "Anus Duang."
How did you know that?
Oh, it was just a guess.
You look like you've got pain in your anus.
No!
I'm all good now.
- Oh, you are?!
- Yes!
Oh, that's good news.
But I'm not asking you to keep his promise.
I just want to fulfill his wishes
so he can rest in peace.
- I see... Is that so?
- Mm.
Hey, Mom.
You may be my mom,
but if you're committing fraud,
I'll arrest you.
What fraud?!
I was just teasing Dobby!
Oh, teasing, huh?
So, can you think of any tenants
who have a relative named Gaysorn?
Danis,
"Auntie Duang" isn't
the Civil Registration Office, you know.
I don't know everything.
I only know a little.
- I see.
I only know who they are,
where they come from,
their partner's name,
what they do for a living, how much they make,
and what they like to eat. That's it.
Wow, you only know a little, huh?
If you knew any more than this...
would you even know
what brand of underwear they wear?
- I do know that about some.
- Huh?!
♫You only one, just you, the only one♫
♫Millions around, no one's like you, baby♫
Singing it wrong, too.
♫Dance a little, black shirt♫
- Hey!
- Ugh!
You're messing with him.
Do you even know him? He's a cop.
- Oh, a cop?
- Mm.
Hello.
Uh, hello...
Hey, you.
What kind of weird role
are you playing this time?
You can't call me that.
You have to call me
"Daisy."
"Daisy"?
- Daisy.
- Daisy...
- Mama.
- Don't call me "you" again.
- Yes, I'm sorry.
- Don't do it again.
Oh, I want to sit down now.
I'm gonna sit down.
Daisy?
Hey,
not like that.
Say "Daisy."
- Daisy?
- Daisy.
- Daisy. Dai...
- sy.
- Ugh!
I know you're Daisy.
That isn't important right now.
Why did you drag your suitcase here?
Oh,
I'm staying with you tonight.
Huh?
I have an acting class
with someone in your dorm.
Who?
Not telling you.
Help! Help! A thief!
- Hey.
Isn't that Dolly?
Yes. Dollar, go!
Dolly!
♫The D Dorm, meet me at the D Dorm♫
♫Every step we take has a meaning♫
♫No path is ever meaningless♫
♫As long as our hearts keep searching♫
♫One day, we'll find
what we're yearning for♫
♫Walking alone is fine,
but it's better when you're by my side♫
♫It won't be lonely
when you're here to walk beside♫
♫Like a love that waits, waits at the D Dorm♫
♫Like a love that remains,
remains at the dorm♫
♫Meaningful love and good things
await on every path♫
♫It might not be a coincidence
that we get to meet♫
♫There might be hidden meanings
on the path beneath our feet♫
♫Perhaps the D Dorm
is what led me to meet you♫
[The D Dorm]
Dolly, are you alright?
Dolly?
- Are you hurt?
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
Go!
- Oh, no, no, no.
- Whoa, whoa.
[Dome, occupation: police officer/drag queen]
Oh, Teach!
Huh?!
They're my
acting teacher.
Huh?!
By the way, you're so cool, Teach.
Catching a thief like that.
See?
We're lucky
Lieutenant Dome was there.
Huh?!
Dollar, who are you
calling Lieutenant Dome?
I'm off duty,
so call me Queen Dominiga.
Huh?!
What is up with you?
You kept saying, "Huh?!"
I can't process this anymore.
Everything is so confusing.
Either way, thank you very much.
If it weren't for you,
I'd be in real trouble.
Hey,
go heavier today.
Look.
- All muscle, no strength to defend yourself!
- Ow!
Go heavier, got it?!
I have muscles,
but the thief had a knife!
How's that my fault?
He got robbed right outside our dorm.
I don't care.
The dorm has to take responsibility.
So, are you gonna
compensate my son or what?!
If you're not gonna pay,
then lower
my rent.
Whoa, Auntie Duang.
I'm truly sorry. We really
don't have enough security guards.
We'll hire more security guards,
but we'll have to raise
the rent too, Auntie Duang.
Hey,
why would you do that?
Keeping our dorm safe
takes all of us working together.
No need to hire more
security guards. It's a waste!
Oh, that's a relief.
You're taking your brother
to file a police report, right?
Take him too, then.
Mm.
Lieutenant Dome is clocking out.
Now it's time for...
"Queen Dominiga" to entertain you!
Are you ready?
I'm so ready, Mama!
Let's go, Daisy.
Follow me!
Hurry up.
- Let's go. How fabulous.
- Let's go.
You're so annoying.
So? What do you think?
The kids in my dorm
are fabulous, are they not?
Whoa.
That's so deep...deep...deep...
Hello...lo...lo...
Whoa, so deep.
Hey, it's so deep.
If you accidentally fall,
no one would know.
♫I-I-I-I'm not scared♫
Hey!
Hurry up.
I'm hungry, and it's hot.
♫Wait a minute, alright, alright?♫
Hey!
Just say it. No need to sing.
♫I don't know how to say it♫
- ♫How to say it♫
- But I know how to kick you.
Dawin!
Couldn't you catch me with your hands?!
My hands?
Look!
Whoa, that's so red.
You were cheering for a football team, huh?
Are you cheering for
the Red Devils or the Reds?
The Red Brat!
I told Daeng
to fix my water heater yesterday.
You call this fixed?
Hot water came out of the sink
and burned my hands like this!
You told me to fix it,
but you never said
which hole the water should come out of.
What? Hey...
You did this on purpose.
Now my hands are like this.
How am I supposed to work?
That's a good thing, isn't it?
Now you won't be able to trick anyone else
with your fortune-telling!
Fine!
Get ready to lose your job,
unhandyman.
Just wait until
Danis hears about this.
I wonder what she'll say.
Mr. Dawin,
please calm down!
Mr. Dawin!
Hurry up and apologize to him.
What are you waiting for?!
♫I'm still free, you know?♫
Hey! Come here.
Go apologize to him!
Whoa!
Fabulous, Mama!
Come help me first. My back hurts.
Don't just sit there
saying "fabulous." Come on.
Okay, sit down first.
Ow, ow, ow, my back...
- Thank you, dear.
- Are you alright?
Dobby,
you're here anyway.
Ask them
if they know Gaysorn.
Um... Dome?
Call me "Queen Dominiga."
- Queen Dominiga...
- That's right.
- Yes.
- Fabulous.
I want to know
if you have a relative named Gaysorn.
My grandpa is looking for his friend.
A relative named Gaysorn...
I don't have a relative with that name.
But if it's a friend, I do have one.
Look, there!
"Queen Tiger Pollen."
See?
It means "Gaysorn (pollen) of a tiger lily."
Does this work for you?
You saw my show earlier, didn't you?
You're so cool.
If I can do that
on my audition day,
I'll definitely get the role.
Alright, stand up.
- Stand up, dear.
- Stand up.
Stand... You, too.
- Oh, I have to stand, too?
- Stand up.
Point your toe.
Both of you.
Look up.
Keep it up, look straight.
Very nice, dear.
Picture yourself as...
a diva.
How about this?
You mamas can practice
while I'll excuse myself.
- Hey, wait!
- Hey, wait, wait, wait.
You have to be here with me.
That way, I'll know...
if I'm fully immersed in my role as Daisy.
You're splendid in this role, Daisy!
I haven't even started yet.
- Dome!
- Oh, no...
The outfit you asked me to fix is ready.
Ooh, here it is!
And this is the food
you ordered from my mom.
- Oh, I was just getting hungry...
- Oh, wow!
You have an audience now.
These two
will stay to help you,
while I have a matter to tend to.
Ms. Danis
has some paperwork for me to sign.
Oh, I have a lot to do.
So I'll have to...
take my leave.
Take care of Dax for me.
What?
Bye-bye.
Oh, please...
Leave him.
You still have time,
so come help me with my student.
- Here. Come.
- Come here, quick.
Come here.
Come, come, come.
Don't just stand there.
- Come.
- Walk!
I can't with you, handsome.
Why? Are your muscles too heavy?
Okay,
time for a vocal warm-up.
Let's start by saying...
♫Wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa♫
Daisy, go.
- ♫Wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa♫
You two, don't just stand there.
All together now.
- ♫Wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa♫
Good!
One more time!
Sign here.
That's all, Mr. Drip.
Here you go.
Thank you so much, Mr. Drip.
I officially welcome you
to 'the D Dorm.'
Thank you for helping me.
I'll pay for your meal, then.
You're welcome.
Don't mind if I do, then.
Auntie Duang!
Yes?
Check, please?
One hundred and twenty baht.
Cool!
Are you dressing up as a milestone?
Whoa, that mouth...
Asking me to burn your room down, huh?
Burn his room down?
If you do that,
the fire's gonna reach your room.
Because your rooms
are right next to each other.
Hey!
Our stores are close,
and now we live next to each other?!
Hey,
when are you gonna stop pestering me, hm?
One hundred and twenty baht.
Yes, Auntie.
Danis!
You'll have to find a new handyman for this dorm.
Why?
Handyman Daeng purposely pranked me
by hooking up hot water to my sink.
See how it burned my hands?!
Whoa...
Ms. Danis,
if you're gonna kick someone out,
kick this scammer tenant out!
Letting him scam people
with fortune-telling like this
is giving the dorm a bad name!
Oh!
You're the scammer!
You burned me with hot water,
clearly trying to kill me!
Ugh! Enough with the two of you.
You're fighting again.
When? Tell me when?!
When will you stop fighting?!
What a headache!
♫There has to be a day, some day♫
♫Two days, three days♫
♫Four days, five days♫
♫Six days, seven days♫
Greetings to my fans.
- This way!
There's a reason I'm singing.
I was trying to cheer you up, Ms. Danis.
Oh?
You're tired, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm tired as well!
Just by walking outside,
I can hear people singing...
♫Thrust a little, black vest♫
♫Thrust, thrust, black vest♫
I was thrusting nonstop, so I'm tired.
And now I have to see
the two of them fighting.
Today is the day
I put an end to this.
Daeng,
will you stop picking fights with Mr. Dawin?
Never!
Mr. Dawin,
will you stop fighting with my brother?
I'll stop
when your brother stops.
We're in the same dorm.
Why don't we love each other?
I don't love you.
I'll ask you two one last time.
Will you change your mind?!
- No!
Then it can't be helped.
What is this?!
- Ow!
- Let go!
Stop. Stop right there.
Guard Dum!
I can report you to the police
for unlawful confinement!
How will you do that
when your phone is right here?
The police station
is ten kilometers from here.
Feel free to shout
if you want a sore throat.
How about this?
If you want me to let you go,
both of you will have to promise me
that you'll stop fighting.
- Never!
Good! Stay there, then.
It's like I have two poodles
welcoming my customers.
I tease you because I love you.
Whoa...
You shouldn't stand too close, then.
Or the poodles will pee on the milestone.
I tease you because I love you.
Oh...I got a taste of my own medicine.
I'll have to ask you
to keep an eye on those two.
- Yes.
- If they're still fighting,
just keep interpreting them.
Interpret what?
"Intertwined."
Aha...
I should get back to work now.
- Yes.
- Don't miss me too much.
- Ugh!
Dum!
- What, Daeng?
- I'm your big brother!
- Let me go!
- Danis!
Ms. Danis!
If someone has a problem
or something breaks,
who's gonna fix it?
Anyone but you, unhandyman!
Oh...
It's you, con artist!
It's you!
- Take this!
- Don't touch me!
- Ugh!
- Oh...
You won't be released tomorrow at this rate!
You!
- You were just making things up
- It's you!
when you read the cards for Mr. Aoftion!
Oh, you're gorgeous, dear.
- Oh, I'm excited.
- So cute.
You're stunning!
Look in the mirror.
- Look at yourself.
- Oh!
- So? Do you like it?
- It's so pretty.
Daisy, let me tell you something.
Wearing makeup
is like burying your old identity
and rebuilding your ideal identity
in its place.
Do you understand?
Yes.
With those huge lashes,
what are you planning to dress as?
A Venus flytrap?
- Oh.
- Hey.
- I'll slap that mouth of yours.
- How dare you.
- Hey!
- That hurts!
That's the style of drag makeup.
Stop eating clean and
try to eat more food for your brain, Dollar.
Oh, how dare you!
- That's right. Get omega three, six, nine, eleven
- Hey...
- Yes.
- to make you smarter.
But if they're that huge,
will you be able to see?
If you're that curious,
why don't you give it a try?
Be a model for my student,
why don't you?
Dolly, go.
Hey.
No need to argue.
You, come here.
Or next time,
I won't exchange my shifts with you.
Fine.
- Go on.
- Come here.
- Hey, dear.
- Yes?
You'll get to see
what real drag is like.
You can't put on the lashes
carelessly, alright?
You have to make it captivating.
Of course.
- Understood?
- Yes.
Did you understand everything I taught you?
I got it.
Good job.
Then I'll excuse myself for a bit.
- Okay.
- Good.
Come here.
Excuse me.
- Come right here.
- Is this a good idea?
- Come here
- Sit, sit, sit.
- Um, I've never...
Sit down. Give it a try.
Let me see.
All done.
Look how beautiful they are.
- Oh, wow.
- It suits you very well.
But why do my eyes...
feel irritated?
Why is that?
When I did it, it felt cool, like normal.
Ow...
- Wait...
- Let me see.
- Let me take a look at the glue
- Here.
Wait, this isn't eyelash glue!
- Huh?
Oh, gosh!
- Take it off, quick!
- Oh, no!
- Slowly, slowly.
- Pull it gently.
Where's Dome?
[Din, occupation:
police officer (Dome's older brother)] อาชีพ
Din...
How did you get here?
Why did you quit being a cop?
Well, I didn't want to be a cop,
but I want to be a drag queen.
Oh, wow.
Hey, Grandpa.
Seriously, if I burn these,
will you receive them?
Probably.
Want a pair of glasses?
Here.
It didn't work, Grandpa.
Put in more effort!
You cannot do it half-heartedly.
Focus on sending it to me.
It is that simple.
But I do not want those things anymore.
I just want the mobile phone.
- The phone?
- Yeah.
What for?
Maybe I will use it to watch
vertical dramas!
Oh, sarcastic, huh?
I just want to call my friends who passed.
I am tired of talking to you all the time.
Oh, wow. Okay.
I'm tired of that, too. Alright.
I'll send it to you.
Buddham aranam
dhammam nasangham talanam.
Huh?
Throwit when yu ar done.
Huh? There's a chant, too?
Throw it when you are done!
- Wait, what?!
- Whoa!
Don't you think the outfits look similar?
Yeah...
- Whoa!
Hey, what's going on?!
- Oh. Whoa.
- Oh.
Hey.
- Dax.
- Ow.
What happened, Dax?
Well,
- Mama Moniga
- Is it dirty?
wants to quit being a cop
and be a drag queen instead.
But their brother wouldn't have it,
so he came to their room.
Yelling and making a huge fuss.
He nearly brought the room down!
You were a cop.
Why did you quit, Dome?
- Look at these outfits.
- Don't pick them up.
I won't let you do
this kind of nonsense again.
Nonsense?
This is the job I love, Din!
And does the job you love
pay the bills?
You'll end up depending on me
or our parents!
Hey...
Calm down, Din.
This is the path
Dome chose.
Stop talking!
You, too.
Who picked those lashes for you?
Seeing them really pisses me off.
Picture this:
if your brother quit being a cop
to do something like this,
would you be okay with that, Dolly?
I'd love that.
Dollar will get to be pretty.
Dolly!
You stop talking.
Stop right there.
But to be honest,
drag queen performers
make a lot of money.
Especially the top performers,
who get paid around
a hundred thousand a month.
Do you think becoming a top performer
is easy?
Not everyone who does this
will end up successful!
I know it's not easy,
but can't I choose to live my life
the way I want?
This is your life,
not a pair of sandals.
You cannot just keep changing things.
Making the wrong choice will ruin your life!
Dome,
you have a bright future.
So why are you risking your future...
with something like this?
At least I'm happy.
You're my brother.
Shouldn't you be happy
when I'm happy?
This is the last time I'm gonna say this.
If you're still going to quit,
then don't call me your brother anymore.
Din.
Dome...
Fine.
Hey, Dome.
Dome...
Dome!
- Dome, wait!
- Dome!
Whoa,
do they really have to cut ties over this?
Yeah...
if I were him,
I would not just
cut ties with them, I am telling you.
I will wait for them
to get what they deserve!
We are older and wiser.
You should listen to what we say!
- Get what they deserve?
- Mm.
Like what you did to Mom?
Dobby...
Who were you talking to?
Your grandpa?
It is not the same.
Those brothers are fighting,
and so are grandpa and grandson.
Daisy has a headache!
Daisy can't take it anymore!
Here.
What?!
I ordered pad kra pao, Auntie.
Why did you give me khanom jeen?
Hey, you're just a prisoner.
What right do you have to choose?
I told her to make khanom jeen for you.
Here.
Your spoon.
Your fork.
If you don't want to starve,
take turns feeding each other, alright?
Come on!
Ms. Danis,
I'm forced to stay handcuffed to him,
and now you're forcing me to feed him, too?
Yes.
Just treat each other better.
- Mm.
- And stop fighting already.
Never!
I can take care of myself.
I don't need his help!
That's what you get
for relying only on luck!
Not your brain.
You have to use a fork!
Look.
Dream on!
There!
Mr. Big Brain,
how are you gonna use your fork now?
What are you looking at?
Want me to feed you? Hm?
- Seriously,
- Hey!
- when are these two
- I didn't get to eat...
- so you don't get to either!
- gonna stop fighting?
Auntie,
it won't be long until
they drop the tough act.
They'll give up soon enough.
But they're being silly
and now fighting with utensils.
That's true, Auntie.
Did they watch too many movies?
Ugh...
Stop.
[The D Dorm]
Oh, wow!
So refreshing!
Very refreshing.
Oh?
What are you looking at?
Are you thirsty?
I'm not giving you this.
Hey...
Ms. Danis,
look at my lips.
They're so dry.
I'll have to say...
♫Water, I need...♫
Ugh!
Why are you singing?
The more you talk,
the more thirsty you'll get.
Danis,
starving us is a bit cruel, don't you think?
When will you let us go?
Oh!
Then make up already.
- Never!
Hey...
Keep on starving, then.
Danis, that's too cruel.
Don't worry, boys.
I'm not going to torture you.
I bought you an ice cold coffee.
Thank you, Auntie.
Here.
Why are the glasses empty?
Where is the coffee?
Here it is.
Your coffee.
Here.
Whoa...
You tied it like those
food in plastic bags.
How am I supposed to untie this?
Help each other out, then.
Lend each other a hand.
The coffee you drink
after facing obstacles and adversities
will taste much sweeter,
aromatic, and delicious.
Hey, give me that!
No need to untie it.
I'll bite the bottom and drink!
Give me that!
Things don't seem to go
as planned, Ms. Danis.
I think...
Should we leave them?
From the looks of it,
they won't make up with each other.
No, Auntie.
We've come this far.
We'll have to see it to the end.
After drinking that much,
they'll have to pee.
And if they still won't make up,
we'll let them pee themselves.
Hm?
They can't do that. This is my restaurant.
Well, it isn't my office.
But won't it stink up my restaurant?
It won't smell in my office.
We can't hear you at all.
Oh, oops.
Oh...
Dobby,
why do you need to
get into their business?
I do not understand.
Just let Dome feel guilty
for not listening to his brother.
Wait, Grandpa.
Dome didn't do anything wrong.
It's his life.
He gets to choose how to live it.
Being an older brother
doesn't mean you can control his life.
Nonsense!
This is not "control."
He just "means well."
Who turned off the lights?!
What...?
Oh...
Is this the pair of glasses
you burned for me?
Don't try to change the topic.
Was pushing my parents out of your house
your way of showing that you meant well?
Yes!
Your mom is stubborn!
And look at her life now.
She is drowning in debts!
Owning a lousy restaurant.
If she would just listen to me...
she wouldn't end up pregnant
by your dad!
If she married the man I found for her,
she would have prospered by now!
Grandpa, when you say that,
does it mean that I was born
to hold Mom back from her fortune?
Dobby, Dobby...
Hey, I...
I did not mean it like that.
Calm down.
What does it mean, then?
Oh, f*ck!
Did you insult me?!
I'm not insulting you.
I'm insulting your outfit.
How the hell did it get here?
- Whoa!
Hey, Dobby!
You...
You have to burn a new outfit for me.
I cannot go around looking like this.
It's embarrassing!
Why would you be embarrassed?
I'm the only person who can see you.
And you won't be embarrassed anymore,
because I'm leaving.
I'm going home!
What about finding Gaysorn?
The search for Grandma Gaysorn?
Mm...
Go ask the others for help, Grandpa.
Because a burden like me,
won't be able to help you.
You are a grown man,
but you still hold a grudge?!
The burden I was talking about
was your father!
You assumed things on your own!
Oh, wow...
I went all in.
Do you ever think that
the reason Mom and Dad left
was because you were
stopping them from being happy?
What would you know?!
The reason I worked so hard
to build this dorm,
it was all for your mother,
so she would be able to live comfortably!
If she was truly happy,
why did she run away?
Well, your mother is stubborn!
She did not want to live
comfortably!
Instead, she ran away to a hard life
with your father in Nakhon Sawan!
You wouldn't understand.
Have you ever gone to check in on Mom
after she ran away?!
How could you know...?
Ugh! Whatever.
I'm going to sell this dorm.
Mom and I don't want to keep it!
Go ahead!
If this dorm
is such an eyesore for you,
then sell it!
And you...
get out!
Get out of here! Go!
Yeah, I'll leave, alright!
Go!
Like mother, like son!
How frustrating!
Hello, Mom, I'm coming home today.
Oh...
I'm a bit sick of seeing
some people at the dorm.
To be honest, I miss your cooking too.
I don't think there will be traffic.
It'll probably take two hours.
Mom,
can I ask you something?
Have you ever regretted
running away to be with Dad?
Huh?!
You regret not taking
Grandpa's money with you?
Huh?
Are you a scammer or something?
Well...you're funny, Mom.
Yeah, I'm on my way.
Miss you.
Muah, muah!
Oh...
Hey...
Dollar,
how did it go?
Did you catch up with Din?
Did you speak for Dome?
Why are you crying?
Did you fight?
I pulled my eyelashes and it hurts.
- Oh...
And...
I don't know where Din went.
We haven't talked.
You don't have to talk to him.
It won't change anything.
In his eyes,
I never grew up.
I'm just a little brother...
who can't think for myself.
A brother who only causes trouble.
Dominiga,
don't be sad.
No matter what people say,
I'll always be by your side.
Just like what NewJiew said,
"If you don't love me, don't act nice
or act like you care."
"If you don't love me,
don't try to protect or order me around."
- "'Cause my heart is fragile."
- Wow...
- That was perfect.
You did that perfectly, dear.
You were dancing, does it mean
that you're not mad at Din anymore?
I wasn't that mad at Din,
but my family is like this.
They put limitations on me
ever since I was young.
Whether it's what I study or what I do...
They never asked if
I'm fine with those things.
Ugh...
Dollar is like that too!
Back then,
he tried to force me into
the Police Cadet Academy.
But I didn't listen.
When he couldn't force me mentally,
he forced me
to exercise physically instead!
- Look.
- Ooh, mm...
- Ugh...
- It's solid.
I was worried about you back then,
because the fashion major
you wanted to get into
didn't look like it could
provide for you.
You must think about your future, too.
If I wasn't here with you,
how will you and Mom live?
Your words are wise,
but your eyelashes are so extra.
Let me take them off for you.
I'll pull them off.
Leave my eyelashes alone!
Hey...
Hey, Dome,
I think Din
didn't want to cut ties with you.
The reason he did that
was because he was worried.
Just like how I'm
worried about Dolly.
I understand,
but I don't think it's fair
Din got to become a police.
He gets to do what he loves.
What about me?
Can't I do something
I love as well?
Then are you sure
that the job you love
can actually sustain you?
Hey, Dominiga,
tell him.
Say it with confidence.
No.
- I lost my footing...
- I'm just saying that
I'll try my best.
Because in his eyes,
working as a drag queen
is an unstable job.
But wouldn't it be better
if I get to do what I truly enjoy?
Your younger brother said it.
What do you think, big brother?
- Huh?
But what if...
it doesn't work out?
What will you do with your life?
I'll have to find a new job, Din.
But not a police.
To be honest,
there is no job
that's a hundred percent stable.
It depends...
on how you live your life.
Din, please give me a chance.
Then we should head home, have a meal,
and talk to our parents about this.
If they disagree,
I'll try to talk to them.
Really?!
- Let's go, then!
- Hey, wait.
You should get changed,
- or our parents might have a heart attack.
- Get changed?
Okay.
- Change your outfit.
- Change, change.
Get changed.
Thank you, Din,
for listening to Dome.
Ugh!
Can I ask you one thing?
Will you remove your eyelashes?
It's annoying to look at.
You don't like it?
No, I don't!
- Stop!
- You don't like it?
Go take them off.
But it's pretty.
Hey, take your friend away.
Hello, this is Daisy.
I was...practicing my script earlier.
Huh?!
You can't contact Dobby?
Dobby.
Are you here?
Oh, why am I hiding?
He cannot see me anyway.
Dobby.
Dobby!
His bag isn't here as well.
How could it be here?
He already went to Nakhon Sawan.
Dobby...
But his car is still here.
Gramps.
Gramps, Gramps.
If you can hear me,
please help me look for Dobby.
His mother is very worried.
Please tell him to call his mother back.
Thank you.
Thank you, Gramps.
What does this have to do with me?!
It is not my duty to look for him!
Maybe I should look for him...
So that he...
burns me a new outfit.
Dobby!
Dobby?
Dobby, where are you?
Dobby!
Hey, do you still exist?
I can't find you anywhere!
Dobby!
Dobby, where are...
Oh?
The manhole cover is open.
Oh...that's dangerous.
Someone might fall in there.
It's probably Daeng the Handyman's fault.
Oh, this is...
Huh?!
Dobby.
Help, please help Dobby!
Hold on, alright?
I will find someone to help you.
Anybody!
Help!
Dobby fell down the sewer!
Dobby!!
Ugh...
why do you have to
keep this up?
Just say you'll make up and
be friends,
and we'll let you go to the toilet.
Yes.
I don't mind doing that.
I can make up with him,
but he has to apologize first!
Oh...
Never...
Ow...
I think we should let them go.
If they pee themselves here,
who will clean it up?
No.
They'll have to clean it on their own.
Think about
what you're going to do next.
Since I'm
not in a rush anyway.
I'll turn on the music while I wait.
♫Let it flow out♫
Everyone!
- Huh?
- Everyone, everyone!
Whoa...
Has anyone seen Mr. Dobby?
What's wrong, Guard Dum?
Mr. Dobby went missing.
- Huh?!
Mr. Dax, Mr. Dolly, and Mr. Dollar were
searching. No one could contact him!
- Everyone, let's go find Dobby!
- Whoa....
- Ow, ow, ow.
- Guard Dum, go!
- Lead the way, Guard Dum.
- Where is he?!
- Quickly!
- Guard Dum, go!
Don't leave yet. Let me go...
Ugh, stop shouting.
The key is right there.
It's so far away,
I can't reach it!
We can, we have to.
Oh!
Put your arm here.
Ow...
Hey!
Whoa!
Duang!
[Duangjai's Kitchen, Made-to-Order Food]
Danis!
Where did they all go?
Come help Dobby!
How can I help him? I can't!
- Gramps?!
You can see me?
Go help Dobby! He fell down the sewer!
A ghost!
Was that real?
What the heck?!
Gramps!
[The D Dorm]
Here's your medicine.
- Ow...
- Thanks a lot.
Whoa.
- It stings...
- Are you really alright?
Whoa.
You got a head injury.
Is your brain still working?
Do you remember who I am?
Would you like me to call you
Dax or Daisy, then?
Oh,
you can call me Daisy.
- Come here, let me give you a smooch.
- Hey!
Dax, stop!
Don't, don't, don't, Dax!
- Dax, don't tease me! Ow!
- Whoa!
- Dax, stop. It hurts!
Am I interrupting something?
I can come back later.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, wait!
- Get off me, Dax!
- What?
- What is it?
- Don't play along.
Oh, okay.
What do you need?
I brought you a first-aid kit.
So after you take a shower,
you can change your bandage.
Oh, you may continue.
- Huh? Don't go yet.
- Wait, wait.
By the way,
I told Daeng the Handyman to
close the manhole cover.
Don't be mad at him, alright?
He didn't mean to be careless.
Just...
Some stuff happened...
Thank you for saving me.
No need to thank me.
You should thank Gramps.
- Huh?
- Mm.
Dawin told me
Gramps suddenly showed up
to tell him that you...
fell down the sewer. And sent him to help you.
Huh?!
Dawin saw Grandpa?
That's what he told me.
Don't believe him too much.
He was probably delirious
from holding in his pee.
- I see...
- Well...
What did he say again?
Gramps was wearing drag
then he...hey!
- Dobby!
- You...
What's wrong, Dobby?
Hey, are you alright?
- Dobby, did you choke?
- I'm fine.
- I'm fine, Ms. Danis.
- Dobby...
But I'm not fine because of you.
What?
- Was it too soft?
- Oh, it's too harsh.
- Hit me gently. It hurts.
- Ugh.
Take care of yourself, then.
I'm tired of you guys.
Hey.
Stop hitting me and go
look for something to help me.
Aw, aren't we going to continue?
That's enough!
Here, I'll dress your wound.
We don't have any Mia cloth.
What? Mia cloth?
Goth.
Wow...
Ow...
- It hurts even worse.
- Oh...
Did you laugh to the point that it hurt?
It's your joke that hurts.
- Let me look around.
- Quickly.
Just find one.
Whoa...
It's a big wound, too.
Is this your house?
Here.
- Whoa.
- Is this kid you?
Dobby, are you hurt?
I am hurt.
Huh?
I fell down a sewer, you know?
You were not asleep?
I couldn't fall asleep, Grandpa.
I want to ask you something.
What?
Ever since Mom went to live with Dad,
have you ever gone to
check in on her?
Why did you go find her, Grandpa?
Didn't you already cut ties with her?
I just wanted to see
the state of her
after she left to be with your father.
You missed my mom, didn't you?
That is none of your business.
What about you?
You said you would go back to
Nakhon Sawan
to that little rat hole house
of yours, did you not?
How can I go back, Grandpa?
Look at me.
Look.
Look!
If I went back looking like this,
your dorm
would be destroyed.
Oh...
Take some rest, then.
I do not want you to perish.
Because if you did,
there will be two ghosts in the same den.
You do not have to thank me.
Just...
burn me a new outfit.
That would be enough.
Because each time I look at this outfit,
it reminds me of a movie.
I cannot recall the name...
The director is called Poj Arnon.
He made a lot of movies.
There is this one scene
in which a character said,
"Who killed Araya"?
And another person answered,
"Payoon..."
Then she went quiet.
And suddenly, she said,
"is not the killer!"
So the other person replied,
"You timed that so horribly"!
Oh, it made me laugh.
I really liked that one.
- Ow, ow...
- It is stuck in my head.
- You...
- Go watch it.
You don't remember the name,
- but you remember all the dialogues?
- Yeah.
But I really enjoyed it.
- You did?
- Yeah.
- I'll go watch it.
I liked it.
Go argue with
yourself outside, Grandpa.
Oh, rest up.
But you have to watch it.
- Yeah, I got it.
- Good.
♫It might not be a coincidence
that we get to meet♫
Call out to him.
Hey!
Ugh.
Stop making loud noises.
It's disturbing other tenants!
Who told you about us?
I did.
Kappa?
- Would you like this, then?!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Dawin!
Why do you want to see
Gramps' ghost again?
I just want to prove
if I have the ability to see ghosts.
I tried it all.
From looking between my legs
to wearing dead people's clothes.
But there's one method I haven't tried yet.
Would you like to try it out tonight?
- Whoa, whoa!
- Ow!
♫The D Dorm, meet me at the D Dorm♫
♫Every step we take has a meaning♫
♫No path is ever meaningless♫
♫As long as our hearts keep searching♫
♫One day, we'll find
what we're yearning for♫
♫Walking alone is fine,
but it's better when you're by my side♫
♫It won't be lonely
when you're here to walk beside♫
♫Like a love that waits, waits at the D Dorm♫
♫Like a love that remains,
remains at the dorm♫
♫Meaningful love and good things
await on every path♫
♫It might not be a coincidence
that we get to meet♫
♫There might be hidden meanings
on the path beneath our feet♫
♫Perhaps the D Dorm
is what led me to meet you♫
[The D Dorm]